Guide to the Yale University Art, Architecture, and Art History Theses and Projects
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Drawings of Donal McLaughlin, 1929-1939; Accession 2005-A-202
  - "A Private Bank", Paris Prize Preliminary (Box 4)
  - "A Shrine" Emerson Prize (Box 4)
  - "Mayan Frontispiece", 1932-33 (Box 4)
  - "A Monumental Clock" Emerson Prize, 1932-33 (Box 4)
  - "Osbourne Planetarium Thesis", 1933 (Box 4)
  - "A University Club" (Box 4)
  - "A Waiting Room of a Railroad station", 1932-33 (Box 4)
  - "A Church", 1934 (Box 4)
  - "A Synagogue", Class A (Box 5)
- Student paper written by Paul Goldberger, Yale College (1972), on Saarinen & others, 1970; Accession 2006-A-041
  - Student paper written by Paul Goldberger, Yale College (1972), on Saarinen & others, 1970 (Box 1)
- Student year end work, M. Arch I [computer files], 2005; Accession 2006-A-043
  - Adengo, Doreen, 2005; 90 computer files (PSD, AI, PDF, JPEG) (Box 1)
  - Albertson, Benjamin, 2005; 38 computer files (PSD, TIFF)
    - Disk 1 of 2 (Box 1)
    - Disk 2 of 2 (Box 1)
  - Ammon, Francesca, Russello* Little City, Big Plans: Stories of Asbury Park, New Jersey, 2005; 19 (Box 1)
  - Barber, Daniel* People's Park: Or, The Crisis of Humanist Architectual Environmentalism, 2005; 1 (Box 1)
  - Bauley, Ralph, 2005; 2 (Box 1)
  - Bingol, Ceren, 2005; 115 computer files (PDF, TIFF, JPEG, DOC) (Box 1)
  - Buck, Brent, 2005; 3 (Box 1)
  - Brott, Simone*, 2005; 173 computer files (DOC, PSD, TIFF) (Box 1)
  - Chen, Yen-Rong*, 2005; 2
  - Conway, Kevin, 2005; 2
  - Cook, Michael, 2005; 81 computer files (JPEG, TIFF)
  - Donovan, Lois, 2005; 17
  - Dudley, William M., 2005; 130 computer files (TIFF)
  - Fein, Christopher, 2005; 7
  - Fletcher, Rosamond* Negotiating the Interface: Communication and Collaboration in Building Technology, From Graphic Manuals to Software, 2005; 2
  - Ford, Mathew, 2005; 10496 computer files (PDF, TIFF, DOC, JPEG, AI, PSD)
  - Forde, Ashley McRainey, 2005; 9
  - Fu, Genevieve, 2005; 1
  - Fullton, James H. III, 2005; 39
  - Gamblin, Jonah, 2005; 1
  - Goldstein, Garth, 2005; 14
  - Gosrisirikul, Charles, 2005; 1
  - Gyuse, Ruth, 2005; 1
  - Hall, Christopher, 2005; 6
  - Hash, Mark, 2005; 54 computer files (TIFF, PDF)
  - Hecht, David, 2005; 3
  - Hoeferlin, Derek, 2005; 2
  - Hong, LiHan*, 2005; 12
  - Hutchinson, Matt, 2005; 4
  - Kim, Jean Y., 2005; 2
  - Lafreniere, Jessie J., 2005; 12
  - Lee, Louis, 2005; 11
  - Lee, Sang Yup, 2005; 5
  - Lee, Lim, 2005; 6
  - Loy, Amanda, 2005; 1
  - Morton, Craig Grant, 2005; 2
  - Newsom, Jennifer, 2005; 1
  - Ozel, Guvenc*, 2005; 2
  - Pace, Brandon, 2005; 7 computer files (PDF, TXT)
  - Poy, Michael Lee*, 2005; 16 computer files (DOC, INDD)
  - Rey, Michael, 2005; 114
  - Ristow, George*, 2005; 1
  - Ruff, Vanessa, 2005; 173 computer files (PSD, PDF, AI, JPEG, TIFF)
  - Shahane, Aniket, 2005; 26 computer files (PDF, TXT)
  - Shepherd, Noah*, 2005; 4
  - Spearman, Brett, 2005; 9
  - Stoutt, Nicholas, 2005; 3
  - Teperman, Yony, 2005; 41 computer files (JPEG, PDF)
  - Walters, Brad*, 2005; 1
  - Wadsworth, Lewis, 2005; 22 computer files (PDF, TIFF, TXT, INDD)
  - Wilson, Sal, 2005; 19
  - Yost, Christopher, 2005; 7
  - Yu, Waiki Tracy, 2005; 4 computer files (PDF, DOC, JPEG)
  - Bergsten, Nora I., 2005 (Box 1)
- Entry for Urban Hall Gerald D. Hines Design Competition, 2005; Accession 2006-A-046
  - Entry for Urban Hall Gerald D. Hines Design Competition, 2005 (Box 1)
- Digital images from "Future Focus: Year End Student Exhibition" [computer files], 2001-2002; Accession 2006-A-081 (Box 1)
  - Digital images from "Future Focus: Year End Student Exhibition", 2001-2002; 282 computer files (PCD, PDF, JPEG)
- Digital images of graduating student posters & portfolios used in "Shift," year end student work [computer files], 2005; Accession 2006-A-129 (Box 1)
  - Ammon, Francesca (MED) -graduate poster, 2005; computer files
  - Atwood, Emily (M.Arch I) -graduate poster and portfolio, 2005; 2
  - Balmanoukian, Garo (M.Arch II) -graduate poster and portfolio, computer files, 2005
  - Barber, Daniel (MED) -graduate poster, 2005; 1
  - Bergsten, Nora (M.Arch I) -graduate poster, 2005; 1
  - Brown, Marissa-year end poster and portfolio, 2005; 2
  - Buck, Brent (M.Arch II) -graduate poster, portfolio and poster from HI Feldman Prize Nominee section -Tod Willams and Billie Tsien Studio, 2005; 3
  - Carruthers, Thomas (M.Arch I) -graduate poster, 2005; 4 computer files (PDF, INDD)
  - Chen, Yen-Rong (M.Arch I) -graduate poster, 2005; 4 computer files (PDF, INDD)
  - Conway, Kevin (M.Arch I) -graduate poster and portfolio, computer files, 2005; 2
  - Cook, Michael (M.Arch I) -graduate poster and portfolio, computer files, 2005; 82 computer files (JPEG, TIFF, DOC)
  - Donovan, Lois (M.Arch II) -graduate poster, 2005; 1
  - Dudley, William (M.Arch I)-graduate poster and portfolio, 2005; 127
  - Fein, Christopher (M.Arch II) -graduate poster, portfolio and poster from HI Feldman Prize Nominee section -Enrique Norton and John Eberhart Studio, 2005; 9
  - Fletcher, Rosamond (MED) -graduate poster, 2005; 2 computer file (1 PDF, 1 INDD)
  - Ford, Mathew (M.Arch I)-graduate poster, 2005; 1
  - Forde, Ashley (M.Arch I)-graduate poster and portfolio, 2005; 11
  - Fu, Genevieve (M.Arch I)-graduate poster and portfolio, 2005; 2
  - Gamblin, Jonah (M.Arch I)-graduate poster, portfolio and poster from HI Feldman Prize Nominee section -Behnisch/Hines studio, 2005; 4
  - Goldstein, Garth (M.Arch I)-graduate poster, 2005; 1
  - Gosrisirikul, Charles (M.Arch I)-graduate poster, 2005; 1
  - Gyuse, Ruth (M.Arch I)-graduate poster, 2005; 20 computer files (JPEG, PDF, INDD)
  - Hall, Christopher (M.Arch II) -graduate poster, portfolio and poster from HI Feldman Prize Nominee section -Jaq Robertson with George Knight, 2005; 6
  - Hanna, Diala (M.Arch II) -graduate poster, 2005; computer files
  - Hoeferlin, Derek (M.Arch II)-graduate poster and portfolio, 2005; 1
  - Hutchinson, Matt (M.Arch II) -graduate poster, portfolio and poster from HI Feldman Prize Nominee section -Gregg Lynn with Mark Gage, 2005; 4
  - Kim, Jean (M.Arch I)-graduate poster and portfolio, 2005; 2
  - Lafreniere, Jesse (M.Arch I)-graduate poster and portfolio, computer files, 2005; 12
  - Lee, Mang Tat Louis (M.Arch I)-graduate poster and portfolio, computer files, 2005; 3
  - Lee, Sangyup (M.Arch II) -graduate poster and portfolio, computer files, 2005; 5
  - Lim, Lee (M.Arch II) -graduate poster and portfolio, 2005; 6
  - Loy, Amanda (M.Arch I)-graduate poster, 2005; 1
  - Newsom, Jennifer -graduate poster and portfolio, 2005; 2
  - Morton, Craig (M.Arch I)-graduate poster and portfolio, 2005; 6
  - Ozel, Guvenc-Greg Lynn Studio Animation, 2005
  - Pace, Brandon (M.Arch II) -graduate poster, portfolio and 2 posters from HI Feldman Prize Nominee section, 2005; 2
  - Rey, Michael (M.Arch I) -graduate poster, portfolio and poster from HI Feldman Prize Nominee section, 2005; 1
  - Ristow, George (M.Arch I)-graduate poster and portfolio, 2005; 2
  - Shepherd, Noah (M.Arch I) -graduate poster, portfolio and poster from HI Feldman Prize Nominee section -Galia Solomonoff studio, 2005; 3
  - Spearman, Brett (M.Arch II) -graduate poster and portfolio, 2005; 10
  - Stanat, Julia (M.Arch II) - Bees graduate poster and portfolio, 2005; 2
  - Stoutt, Nicholas (M.Arch I) -graduate poster and portfolio, 2005; 3
  - Sung, Young Mo (M.Arch I) -graduate poster and portfolio, 2005; 2 computer files (PDF, JPEG)
  - Teperman, Yory (M.Arch I) -graduate poster and portfolio, 2005; 41 computer files (38 JPEG, 3 PDF)
  - Van Nest, Jason (M.Arch I) -graduate poster, 2005; 1
  - Wadsworth, Lewis (M.Arch I)-graduate poster and portfolio, computer files, 2005; 22 computer files (TIFF, PDF)
  - Wilson, Sal (M.Arch I)-graduate poster, 2005; computer files
  - Yoo, Jiwon (M.Arch I)-graduate poster and portfolio, 2005; 1
  - Yost, Christopher (M.Arch II)-graduate poster and portfolio, 2005; 7
  - Yu, Wai-Ki (M.Arch II)-graduate poster and portfolio, 2005; 4 computer files (2 PDF, 1 DOC, 1 JPEG)
- Master of Environmental Design theses by Ammon, Barber, and Fletcher, 2005; Accession 2006-A-158
  - Ammon, Francesca Russello., 2005 (Box 1)
  - Barber, Daniel., 2005 (Box 1)
  - Fletcher, Rosamond., 2005 (Box 1)
- Student work from M.Arch I and M.Arch II degree programs [computer files], 2006; Accession 2007-A-002
  - 1. Brian Hopkins, 2006; 2 (Box 1)
  - 2. Benay Betts, 2006; 7 (Box 1)
  - 3. Allan William Martin, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 4. Michael Grogan, 2006; 8 (Box 1)
  - 5. Maxwell Morrell, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 6. Susan Parapetti, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 7. Joyce Chang, 2006 (Box 1)
  - 8. Namil Byun, 2006; 47 computer files (45 JPEG, 1 PDF, 1 INDD (Box 1)
  - 9. Mark Davis [empty], 2006 (Box 1)
  - 10. Naomi Darling, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 11. Christopher Kitterman, 2006; 48 computer files (PDF, INDD) (Box 1)
  - 12. Marina Dayton, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 13. Scott Baltimore, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 14. Roy Griffith, 2006; computer files (Box 1)
  - 15. Jennifer Duhamel, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 16. Brent Fleming, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 17. Melanie Domino, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 18. E. Younha Rhee, 2006; 47 (Box 1)
  - 19. Tim Kirkby, 2006; 180 computer files (PDF, INDD, TIFF, JPEG, AI) (Box 1)
  - 20. Eron Ashley, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 21. Tim Campbell [empty], 2006 (Box 1)
  - 22. Marisa Kurtzman, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 23. Drake Hawthorne, 2006; computer files (Box 1)
  - 24. Matt Byers, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 25. Michael Lavery, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 26. Julia McCarthy, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 27. Louise Milliken Smith, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 28. Eren Ciraci, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 29. Paolo Campos, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 30. Allan Ashton, 2006; 4 (Box 1)
  - 31. Katherine Burke [empty], 2006 (Box 1)
  - 32. Aaron Fox, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 33. Nicole Lambrou, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 34. Meaghan Smialowski, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 35. Russell Greenberg, 2006; computer files (Box 1)
  - 36. Andrei Harwell, 2006; 26 computer files (JPEG) (Box 1)
  - 37. Adam Ganser, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 38. Daniel Chung, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 39. Mayur Mehta, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 40. Nathan Hume, 2006; 81 computer files (TIFF) (Box 1)
  - 41. Chris Dial, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 42. Abigail Coover, 2006; 95 (Box 1)
  - 43. A. Lyon, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 44. Fred Scharmon, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 45. Dariel Cobb, 2006; 17 computer files (16 PDF, 1 JPEG) (Box 1)
  - 46. Ross Smith, 2006; 43 (Box 1)
  - 47. Abigail Ransmeier, 2006; 293 computer files (PDF, JPEG) (Box 1)
  - 48. Armand Graham, 2006; 2 (Box 1)
  - 49. Laura Killam Studio, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  - 50. Laura Killam Final, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
- Student work, School of Architecture, circa 1954-1988; Accession 2007-A-192
  Student records in bBox 1 restricted until January 1, 2057 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
  - Student theses, 1964-1982 (Box 1)
    Student records are restricted until January 1, 2057 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
  - Student projects, 1964-1982 (Box 2)
  - Michael Sackler, New Haven Animal Hospital; David Bolger, undated (Box 3)
  - Matthews, undated (Box 4)
  - Miles Iveintraub, Studio for Sculptor; Stephen Bross; Yusak Chang, undated (Box 5)
  - Creative Arts Workshop, 1974 (Box 6)
  - E. McClintock, Firehouse; James R. Harrington, undated (Box 7)
  - T. Gora Hansen, Frankel House; Jeff Gold; Umberto Brandigi, King Street Elementary School, undated (Box 8)
  - M. Hlalu, Urban Foundation; Barber, undated (Box 9)
  - Pieuthuer Thesis; Robert Faesy, undated (Box 10)
  - Yale Club Ski Lodge (Box 11)
  - Boy's Camp Site (Box 12)
  - House in Branford, CT (Box 13)
  - 56 Hill House (Box 14)
  - Library and Small Auditorium (Box 15)
  - Historical Exhibition, 1960? (Box 17–18)
  - Arch 11 (Box 16)
  - Archives Building, Arch 21, 1954 (Box 16)
  - Drawings from freehand class, undated (Box 19)
  - Dormitories (Box 20)
  - Blume, Johnson, Menzer, and Heeden: Summer house, studio (Box 21)
  - House in Fairfield, CT (Box 22)
  - Miller, Jones, and Coutiss, undated (Box 23)
  - Yale Art Gallery Replanning (Box 24)
  - Housing, Hartford, Millelstadt (Box 25)
  - Peter Vercelli, Council chamber, circa 1960-1970 (Box 26)
  - Yale University Chapel, 1957 (Box 27)
  - C. Spencer, 1982 (Box 28)
  - Produce Market, 1954 (Box 29)
  - Country Club, Gerald Oudens, 1957 (Box 30)
  - James Jarret Padavic, Midtown Manhattan Retail, 1955 (Box 31)
  - Bathroom Sketch Problem, 1961 (Box 32)
  - Lighthouse Point Carousel Pavilion (Box 33)
  - Room Studies
    - college room, 1958 (Box 34)
    - colonial room, 1958
    - bedroom, 1958
  - Auditorium, academic, library, undated (Box 35)
  - Ir Zaenvdin Kartadiwiria, 1967 (Box 36)
  - J.G. Harvey, thesis project, 1962 (Box 37)
  - Arch 11a, 1955 (Box 38)
  - R. Marks and Hagenah, Thesis project, 1962 (Box 39)
  - Carpenter Center (Box 40)
  - Arch 13 (Box 41–46)
    - A. Housten, 1963
    - R. Devans, 1963
    - Wood Lockhart, 1963
    - Bill Drenan, 1963
    - Geoffry palmer, 1963
    - Gerrard Ives, 1963
    - Robert Kuehn, 1963
    - Sephen Freeman, 1963
    - Robert Field, 1963
    - S.C. Whitaker, 1963
    - Debretteville, 1963
    - Brolin, 1963
    - Lawrence Golz, 1963
    - H. Fraser Mills, 1963
    - Andrea Kruger, 1963
    - Angus McDonald, 1963
    - A.M. Weber, 1963
    - John Lucas, 1963
    - R. Giegengack, 1963
    - Theodore P. Streibert, 1963
    - Fred Andreae, 1963
    - W.S. Evans, 1963
    - Ralph Carlson, 1963
    - Howard Phillips, 1963
    - Enrique Senior, 1963
    - E.R. Bolsinger, 1963
    - David Rhyan, 1963
    - R.M. Donnely, 1963
    - Robert Allen Bell, 1963
    - Johnathen Rose, 1963
    - Christina Wilhelm, 1963
    - Barry Simpson, 1963
    - Louis Mackall, 1963
    - Clark Andreae, 1963
    - Gary Watrous, 1963
    - Scott Mayorea, 1963
    - Yugi Noga, 1963
    - E. Ives, 1963
    - D. Bulazzi, 1963
  - Historical exhibitions, undated (Box 47–49)
  - Student union, auditorium, undated (Box 50)
  - W. Liacas and Tam, Thesis project, 1964 (Box 51)
  - T.H. David and Bolton, Thesis project, 1964 (Box 52)
  - Martin and Baggley, Thesis project, 1964 (Box 53)
  - E. Hedeen and Earl Quenneville, Site Plan for Recreation Center/Community Center, 1955 (Box 54)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 55)
  - Der Scutt, Rehabillitation Center for Hospital Complex, 1960 May (Box 56)
  - Der Scutt, Thesis: Fortworth Museum, 1961 (Box 56)
  - Stanley Tigerman, Apartment Hotel for Chicago, 1959-1960 (Box 56)
  - Charles Gwathmey, Pierson-Sage Science Community at Yale, circa 161 (Box 57)
  - M.A. Hansen, USA Dining Hall, 1961 October 23 (Box 57)
  - S.V. Parangre, undated (Box 57)
  - Carl Abott, A Residence in Palm Beach, 1961-1962 (Box 57)
  - Charles Gwathmey, undated (Box 57)
  - Charles P. Hagenah, Colgate University Library, undated (Box 57)
  - T.L. Bosworth, 1957 (Box 58)
  - Unidentified (Box 59)
  - Phyllis Lambert, Weir 2, 2 drawings (lower level; elevations), 1959 April 10 (Box 60)
- Master of Environmental Design theses, 2006; Accession 2007-A-208
  - Knoblauch, Joy, "Architecture and Contingent Subjectivity", 2006 May 18 (Box 1)
  - Ryan, Leslie Ann, "Seeing through Water", 2006 May (Box 1)
  - Stevens, Sara, "Systems of Retail: The Bigger Box", 2006 May 18 (Box 1)
- Student work from M.Arch I and M.Arch II degree programs [computer files], 2007; Accession 2007-A-210 (Box 1)
  - M.Arch I
  - 01. Anya A. Grant, 2007; 1
  - 02. Geoffrey Lawson, 2007; 5
  - 03. Young-Jin Lee, 2007; 1
  - 04. Heather Loeffler, 2007; 1
  - 05. Elise Lui, 2007; 1
  - 06. Mako Maeno, 2007; 10
  - 07. Jeffrey McBride, 2007; 1
  - 08. Seung Namgoong, 2007; 1
  - 09. Mathew Razook, 2007; 1
  - 10. Jeffrey Richards, 2007; 1
  - 11. Neil Sondgeroth, 2007; 1
  - 12. Ayumi Sugiyama, 2007; 8
  - 13. Weston Walker, 2007; 1
  - 14. Kwok Yiu Wan (Vincent), 2007; 181 computer files (JPEG)
  - 15. Lindsay Weiss, 2007; 1
  - 16. William West, 2007; 1
  - M.Arch II
  - 17. Mohammed Balilia, 2007; 1
  - 18. Katherine Corsico, 2007; 1
  - 19. Jason de Boer, 2007; 1
  - 20. Yoo Jong Lee, 2007; 1
  - 21. Timothy Newton, 2007; 2
  - 22. Carol Ann Ruiz, 2007; 1
  - 23. Julia Suh, 2007; 3
- Student projects, 2005; Accession 2007-A-231
  - Byun, Namil, Sung Ik Cho, Mario A. Cruzate, Michael Grogan, Andrei Harwell, Brian Hopkins, Christopher Kitterman, Sean Khorsandi, Mayur Mehta, Frank Melendez, Dadiv Nam, and Mawxwell Worrell, "Issues in Architecture and Urbanism," Course 717A, Post Pro Seminar, instructor Fred Koetter, 2005 Fall (Box 1)
  - Coover, Abigail, Hathan Hume, Armand, Graham, and Adam Ganser, "Fabrication + Effects," independent study project, instructor Mark Gage, 2005; 65 computer files (JPEG, TIFF, PDF, AI, INDD)
- Masters of Environmental Design theses, 2007; Accession 2008-A-166
  - Clutter, McLain, "Imagineering New York: Film Production and Urban Planning Policy, 1966-1975", 2007 (Box 1)
  - Eversole, Britt, "Progetto e Impero: The Critical Project of Contropiano", 2007 (Box 1)
  - Ramirez III, Enrique Gualberto, "Built to Destroy: Erich Mendelsohn's, Konrad Wachsmann's, and Antonin Raymond's "Typical German and Japanese Test Structures" at Dugway Proving Ground, Utah", 2007 (Box 1)
  - Rosenberg, Frida, "Shifting Identity, in Swedish Urban Structure from Folkhemmet to Globalization", 2007 (Box 1)
  - Steenson, Molly Wright, "The Architect, the Sketch and the Response: construing and Constructing Cedric Price's Generator", 2007 (Box 2)
  - Vannucchi, Federica, "Superstudio: Discorsi per Immagini", 2007 (Box 2)
- Class of 2008 student portfolios from M.Arch I and M.Arch II [computer files], Accession 2009-A-051 (Box 1)
  - 01.Axley, Claire Cole, 2008; 1
  - 02.Baldwin, Elizabeth Virginia, 2008; 8
  - 03.Berrun, Moises, 2008; 2
  - 04.Bosschaert, Anton Nikolaas, 2008; 1
  - 05.Burr, Alexandra McCallum, 2008; 1
  - 06.Butler, Alexander Stewart, 2008; 2
  - 07.Cartwright, Gene Stroupe, 2008; 2
  - 08.Chan, Jamie Alma, 2008; 1
  - 09.Colakis, Minna, 2008; 1
  - 10.Corbett, Christopher Martin, 2008; 1
  - 11.Crockett, Michael Beaumont, 2008; 1
  - 12.Cielo, Jonathon Matthew, 2008; 1
  - 13.DiNatale, Charles Thomas, 2008; 2
  - 14.Dubon, Jennifer Jacqueline, 2008; 1
  - 15.Fenton, Todd Griffith, 2008; 64 computer files (60 PSD, 2 exe, 1 inf, 1 rcl)
  - 16.Gantner, Garret James, 2008; 1
  - 17.Geldart, Jeff J, 2008; 188 computer files (1 TXT, 1 INDD, 10 AIFF, 10 PDF, 3 TIFF, 163 JPEG)
  - 18.Getman, Dana, 2008; 2
  - 19.Guberman, Marc Charles, 2008; 1
  - 20.Ho, Gabrielle, 2008; 1
  - 21.Hoffman, Mark C, 2008; 1
  - 22.Knox, Alan, 2008; 2
  - 23.Kim, Gemma, 2008; 4
  - 24.Kraal, Ireta S H, 2008; 7
  - 25.Kraus, Whitney Meryl, 2008; 1
  - 26.Krop, Michael Thomas, 2008; 1
  - 27.Marasso, Lorenzo (M. Arch II), 2008; 1
  - 28.Martin, Brent Caldbick, 2008; 1
  - 29.McDermott, Nicholas W, 2008; 1
  - 30.Melniciuc, Maria Claudia, 2008; 1
  - 31.Miller, Lydia J F, 2008; 1
  - 32.Murado-Arias, Sara, 2008; 1
  - 33.Newman, Marc C, 2008; 2
  - 34.Nielson, Stephen J, 2008; 1
  - 35.Ogasahara, Nobuki, 2008; 1
  - 36.Omoto, Garrett Thomas, 2008; 1
  - 37.Pilo, Amrit Eapen (M. Arch II), 2008; 2
  - 38.Powers, Michael Shawn (M. Arch II), 2008; 2
  - 39.Pytko, Jason, 2008; 2
  - 40.Reynoldson, Pierce Allen, 2008; 2
  - 41.Rich, Nathan David, 2008; 1
  - 42.Riedel, David J, 2008; 17
  - 43.Rubino, Christopher Michael, 2008; 1
  - 44.Schroeder,EricaRachel, 2008; 15
  - 45.Steffen, Andrew James (M. Arch II), 2008; 1
  - 46.Stevens, Leo Rowling, 2008; 2
  - 47.Strackbein, Isaac John, 2008; 2
  - 48.Stutts, Kathryn Lee, 2008; 2
  - 49.Tan, Chiew Hong, 2008; 92
  - 50.Tayler, Aaron Payne (M. Arch II), 2008; 1
  - 51.Truong, Quang Vinh, 2008; 2
  - 52.Varner Lupo, Jessica Ann, 2008; 1
  - 53.Van Brocklin, Mark, 2008; 193 computer files (80 PDF, 3 PSD, 6 BMP, 95 JPEG, 9 TIFF)
  - 54.Wu, Christina, 2008; 1
  - 55.Zamora, Alberto Briseno, 2008; 3
- Class of 2009 and 2010 student portfolios for M.Arch I and M.Arch II [computer files], Accession 2010-A-095 (Box 1–2)
  - Class of 2009
    - Beale, Angel, 2009
    - Berg, Jamie, 2009
    - Berkas, Bryan, 2009
    - Beyer, Rebecca, 2009
    - Brough, John Capen, 2009
    - Cheng, Shu, 2009
    - Chew, Terrence, 2009
    - Chow, Christine, 2009
    - Chua, Cheng Hui, 2009
    - Ciprian, Dexter, 2009
    - Cole, R.H., 2009
    - Cucco, Marc, 2009
    - Davis, Cody, 2009
    - Eby, Travis, 2009
    - Garcia, Isidro, 2009
    - Gathinji, Mwangi, 2009
    - Gausepohl, M.R., 2009
    - Godeken, Leslie, 2009
    - Hanna, Nicholas, 2009
    - Herzl, Reuben, 2009
    - Khalili, Parsa, 2009
    - Kim, Jason J., 2009
    - King, Isaiah, 2009
    - Levi, Louise, 2009
    - Lewandowski, Josh, 2009
    - Lum, Patrick, 2009
    - Martin, Felicia, 2009
    - Maymind, Alex, 2009
    - Mello, Marianna, 2009
    - Mueller, Kristin, 2009
    - Neufeld, Shane, 2009
    - Park, Cheon-kang, 2009
    - Peterson, Miriam L., 2009
    - Reese, Rachel, 2009
    - Rizvi, Karen, 2009
    - Roman, Matthew, 2009
    - Sami, Saifullah, 2009
    - Snider, Zakery, 2009
    - Snyder, Trisha, 2009
    - Spigle, Meghan, 2009
    - Tang, Tom, 2009
    - Von Zumbusch, Julianna, 2009
    - Wells, Emily Arden, 2009
    - Yang, G., 2009
    - Yoder, D., 2009
  - Class of 2010
    - Anderson, C, 2010
    - Appel, Brett, 2010
    - Armstrong, Anne-marie, 2010
    - Ashey, Andrew, 2010
    - August-Schmidt, Julianne, 2010
    - Blacksher, Amina, 2010
    - Bond, Jason, 2010
    - Brown, Helen, 2010
    - Burke, Joel, 2010
    - Burns, Talley, 2010
    - Chang, Christine, 2010
    - Chapple, Craig, 2010
    - Chuan, Harvey, 2010
    - Cojocaru, Andreea, 2010
    - Collman, Cory, 2010
    - Conner, Patrick, 2010
    - Crosson, Courtney, 2010
    - Doyle, Aldan J., 2010
    - Evans, Kurt, 2010
    - Farewell, Aurora, 2010
    - Fernandes De Mesa, Alejandro, 2010
    - Garnetti, Rebecca, 2010
    - Geraki, P., 2010
    - Gharagozloo, Tala, 2010
    - Gilliland, 2010
    - Haferd, Jerome, 2010
    - Hawkins, Jacquelyn, 2010
    - Higgins, Eliza, 2010
    - Howard, Paul, 2010
    - Jomini, Jude, 2010
    - Knapp, K. Brandt, 2010
    - Kori, Leyla, 2010
    - Lee, Jang Hyung, 2010
    - Lee, Jang Won, 2010
    - Linville, Caleb, 2010
    - Liu, Nina, 2010
    - Marks, Aram, 2010
    - McDaniel, Meredith, 2010
    - Mills, Ian, 2010
    - O'Daniel, Scott, 2010
    - Patell, Cyrus, 2010
    - Persinger, Matthew, 2010
    - Peterson, David, 2010
    - Pursley, Zachariah, 2010
    - Raspall, Felix, 2010
    - Sattler, Meredith, 2010
    - Singer, Francesca, 2010
      Contact Public Services (phone: 203 432-1735, e-mail: mssa.assist@yale.edu) for information on accessing this digital object.
    - Smierzchalski, Tomek, 2010
    - Starkey, 2010
    - Stevens, Zachary, 2010
    - Thatcher, Kate, 2010
    - Tomski, Adam, 2010
    - Travieso, Chet, 2010
    - Velten, Tyler, 2010
    - Vittadini, Andrea, 2010
    - Wang, Yu, 2010
    - Wu, Juenan, 2010
    - Ybarra, Steve, 2010
    - Zaic, Hilary, 2010
    - Zedillo, Carlos, 2010
  - Marrakech Studio, 2010
    - Marrakech Studio, 2010
- Two ink and graphite drawings for the Art and Architecture Collaborative of Zoo Habitats by William S. Huff, 1951; Accession 2012-A-031
  - Drawing I--Plan at Ground Level and Plan at Upper Main Level, 1951 (Box 1)
  - Drawing II—Section, 1951 (Box 2)
- Art, architecture, and art history theses and projects, 1951-1952; Accession 2012-A-089
  - The "Collaborative Art and Architectural Zoo" assignment for the class of Frederick A. Kiesler in Architecture at the School of Fine Arts, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Architectural engineering courses and state boards taken by William S. Huff, 1949-1953; Accession 2012-A-090
    - Architectural Engineering State Board records and academic work for structural (architectural) engineering courses, 1949-1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Class of 2011 and 2012 portfolios [computer files], 2007-2012; Accession 2012-A-099
  - Andrachuk, James, 2011-2012 (Box 1)